const awareness = [
    {
        question: "Which state got the GI tag on Kadkanath chicken?",
        answers: ["Madhya Pradesh", "Chhattisgarh", "Bihar", "Tamil Nadu"],
        correct: "Madhya Pradesh"
        },
        {
        question: "Which state did the GI tag on Robusta coffee?",
        answers: ["Kerala", "Karnataka", "BiharTelengana", "Bihar"],
        correct: "Kerala"
        },
        {
        question: "Which state got the GI tag on Sirsi Supari?",
        answers: ["Bihar", "Karnataka", "Odisha", "Himachal pradesh"],
        correct: "Karnataka"
        },
        {
        question: "Himsagar is an extremely popular mango cultivator, origination from_____",
        answers: ["Kerala", "Rajesthan", "Haryana", "West Bengal"],
        correct: "West Bengal"
        },
        {
        question: "Pokkali rice cultivated in?",
        answers: ["Uttar Pradesh", "Tamil nadu", "Kerala", "Maharashtra"],
        correct: "Kerala"
        },
        {
        question: "Feni is a spirit produced exclusively in",
        answers: ["Telengana", "Tamilnadu", "Andhra Pradesh", "Goa"],
        correct: "Goa"
        },
        {
        question: "What is the time limit of GI tag?",
        answers: ["10 years", "20 years", "50 years", "unlimited time"],
        correct: "10 years"
        },
        {
        question: "Who issues Gi tag in India",
        answers: ["1. Ministry of commerce and Industry", "2. Department of Industry promotion and International Trade", "3. Ministry of Tourism", "Both 1 and 2", "4. Ministry of Finance, Govt. of India"],correct: "Both 1 and 2"
        },
        {
        question: "Mahabaleshwar strawberry got GI tag?",
        answers: ["Uttar Pradesh", "Maharashtra", "Madhya Pradesh", "Tamil nadu"],
        correct: "Maharashtra"
        },
        {
        question: "Queen Pineapple got GI tag ?",
        answers: ["Tripura", "Andhrapradesh", "Mizoram", "Manipur"],
        correct: "Tripura"
        },
        {
        question: "Patola Sari got GI tag ?",
        answers: ["Gujrata", "Odisha", "West Bengal", "Karnataka"],
        correct: "Gujrata"
        },
        {
        question: "Makrana Marble got GI tags?",
        answers: ["Rajasthan", "Madhya Pradesh", "Andhra Pradesh", "Gujrata"],
        correct: "Rajasthan"
        },
        {
        question: "Chanderi sari got GI tag ?",
        answers: ["Karnataka", "Uttar Pradesh", "Madhya Pradesh", "Bihar"],
        correct: "Madhya Pradesh"
        },
        {
        question: "Dindigul Locks got G.I Tags?",
        answers: ["Tamil Nadu", "Odisha", "Uttar-pradesh", "Andhra Pradesh"],
        correct: "Tamil Nadu"
        },
        {
        question: "Palani Panchamirtham GI tag?",
        answers: ["Odisha", "Tamil Nadu", "Kerala", "West Bengal"],
        correct: "Tamil Nadu"
        },
        {
        question: "Gulbarga Tur Dal GI tags?",
        answers: ["Odisha", "Karnataka", "Bihar", "Madha Pradesh"],
        correct: "Karnataka"
        },
        {
        question: "Which state did the GI tag match on Marayoor jagary",
        answers: ["Kerala", "Bihar", "Andhra Pradesh", "Uttar Pradesh"],
        correct: "Kerala"
        },
        {
        question: "Match the following products from the correct state in sequence which got the GI tag? Sangli mango-Shahi lichi-Silk sari-Kandhamal turmeric",
        answers: ["Maharashtra-Bihar-Tamil nadu-Odisha", "Maharashtra-Bihar-Telengana-Odisha", "Kerala-Tamil nadu-Bihar-Odisha", "Odisha-Maharastra-Tamil nadu-Himachal Pradesh"],
        correct: "Maharashtra-Bihar-Tamil nadu-Odisha"
        },
                     
]